moneygram.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Statement U.S.

**  
STATE PRIVACY LAWS**  
We will comply with state privacy laws to the extent they apply to MoneyGram services.

**California residents:** In accordance with California law, we will not share information we collect about you with companies outside of MoneyGram except as required or permitted by law. For example, we may share information to service your accounts, complete requested transactions, or to provide rewards or benefits to which you are entitled.

**Nevada residents:** This notice is provided to you pursuant to state law. Nevada state privacy laws permit us to make marketing calls to existing customers, but if you prefer not to receive marketing calls, you may be placed on our internal opt-out list by calling us at 1-800-926-9400 or you may also contact the Nevada Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Ste 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101; telephone 702-486-3132; email: [BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us.](mailto:BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us)

**Texas residents:** If you have a complaint, first contact MoneyGram Payment Systems, Inc., at 1-800-926-9400 . If you still have an unresolved complaint regarding the company’s money transmission or currency exchange activity, please direct your complaint to the Texas Department of Banking: 2601 North Lamar Boulevard, Austin, TX 78705-4294; 1-877-276-5554 (toll free); [www.dob.texas.gov](mailto:http://www.dob.texas.gov).

**Vermont residents:** In accordance with Vermont law, we will not share information we collect about you with companies outside of MoneyGram except as required or permitted by law. For example, we may share information to service your accounts, complete requested transactions, or to provide rewards or benefits to which you are entitled.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY  
**Our website is not directed at children under the age of 13. MoneyGram does not knowingly collect or maintain information from persons under the age of 13.

**EXTERNAL WEBSITES  
**Our website may be linked to or from third party websites. MoneyGram is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of websites that are linked to or from our website.

**COOKIES  
**Some of our web pages may contain "cookies," or data which are sent to your web browser and stored on your computer. [For information about MoneyGram’s use of cookies, please visit our Cookie Policy](http://corporate.moneygram.com/cookies-policy "MoneyGram Cookies").

**ADVERTISING ON THIRD-PARTY SITES  
**MoneyGram may use one or more third-party advertising service providers to display our advertising on third-party sites to users who may have an interest in our products, services or promotions. If you visit our site or show interest in our products, we may use those providers to serve banner ads or other advertising to you when you are on other sites. Those providers may use information such as web pages visited, search keywords entered, your activities on our site, or your responsiveness or interest in our email promotions to make that determination. To learn more about the use of this information or to make choices about receiving personalized advertising provided by third parties, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>.

MoneyGram also allows third parties (affiliates or nonaffiliates) to collect personal information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across different websites when a consumer uses MoneyGram’s website or service.

 **“DO NOT TRACK” SIGNALS  
**MoneyGram does not respond to web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personal information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services.

**CHANGES  
**MoneyGram reserves the right to modify this Privacy Statement. To the extent required by applicable law, we will notify you and give you the opportunity to opt out of any material change in the way we use or disclose personal information you previously have provided. You can get an updated Privacy Statement by calling us at or 1-800-926-9400 or by visiting our website at www.moneygram.com.
